CLASS	        BUFFS	                                                                                        NERFS	                                                            SPECIALS
			
BARBARIAN	    Strength increase. More health.	Very slow.                                                      Short sighted.	Receive less damage.                                Increase damage given.
BARD	        Unnoticed by mobs.  Double Jump. Fast	                                                        Less Health. Can't use Netherrite.	                                Attracts passive animals as meat shields.
CLERIC	        Mine a lot faster. Night Vision.	                                                            Viewing distance shorter. Less attack damage.	                    Burst of healing spell.
DRUID	        Every taiimed animal adds a heart (capped at 5). Regen in the light.	                        Can't swim. Hunger in dark enviroments.	                            Can turn into an animal they've killed.
FIGHTER	        High health. High Strength.	Attracts mobs.                                                      Can't use bows. No potions.	                                        Super regen.
MONK	        Less armor = more damage. Fast fist action. Staff +10 attack (Rare). Speed 1.	                Weakness on anything but a staff.	                                Fast hitters for a period of time.
PALADIN	        Natural smite enchartment. High health.	                                                        No potions. Extremely weak in nether.	                            Self heal.
RANGER	        2x Zoom using a bow and natural power. Natural Looting.	                                        Can't use swords. Every fire is blue fire.	                        Machine gun bow.
ROGUE	        No poison damage. No hunger.	                                                                Nether mobs are alies but all overworld mobs will attempt to kill.	Invisibility for a period.
NECROMANCER	    Wither debuff to all attacked. Not attacked by undead.	                                        Less Health. Less attack damage.	                                Spawn allied undead that attack foe.
WARLOCK	        Slow fireball. Resistent to all fire and lava.	                                                Fire tick damage in water & rain.	                                Breathe fire.
WIZARD	        "Elemental staffs scattered; Fireball, Lightning, Ice (freeze enemies)"	                        Half health. Max Iron armor.	                                    Nuclear bomb + blast resistance.
ARTIFICER	    Speed increase. Automatic enchanting chance or Armor upgrade.	                                Less damage. Uneffected by bonus potions (unless an ability)	    Armor buff for a period of time.
BLOOD HUNTER    Fire aspect on all swords. x2 Damage during Night.	                                            Swords cannot be dropped. 1/2 Damage during the Day.	            Takes control of ANY mob within 30m (including players).
ALCHEMIST	    Craft special potions. e.g. Mob fight mob potion. Anxiety Potion. Immune to poison and wither.	Random potion backfire.                                             1/5	Spam potions of strength and healing.

Barbarian - warrior armour
Bard - assassin_armor
Cleric - silver_knight
DRUID - Wooden armour
FIGHTER - knight_armor 
MONK - robe armour
PALADIN holy armour
RANGER - sunset_wings_armor
ROGUE - rogue
NECROMANCER - wither armour
WARLOCK - golden horns armour
ARTIFICER - steampunk_armor 
ALCHEMIST - prismarine_armor